We'll take advantage of what the framework offers in order to build our
SettingsActivity. Since we're supporting Gingerbread devices,
we'll use a preference activity class. If you're targeting Honeycomber later,
you'll want to use the PreferenceFragment class.
Create a new SettingsActivity class from the gist provided below.
Update the AndroidManifest to declare this new activity. You can see the way
detail activity is declared as an example. If you see that APIs are deprecated,
that's okay. That's a side effect of using PreferenceActivity, in order
to target Gingerbread devices. When you create your app for your final project,
you can use the wizard in Android Studio to create a new SettingsActivity.
The code the wizard provides will make your app backward compatible,
by using a combination of preference activity and PreferenceFragment.
Our gist is meant to be a simplified version of that for learning purposes. So
later, you'd be able to understand better what the wizard is doing.
Check these items off when you're done.